{
    "subject": "resource/Duchy_of_Brunswick",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Braunschweig",
    "human_readable": "The capital of the Duchy of Brunswick is Braunschweig.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9112597703933716,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8621060848236084,
            "question": "What city served as the capital for the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8588961958885193,
            "question": "Braunschweig was the capital of which historical territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8235490322113037,
            "question": "What is the name of the capital city in the context of the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7183366417884827,
            "question": "If you were to visit the historical capital of the Duchy of Brunswick, what city would you go to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7166924476623535,
            "question": "Name the capital of the historical region known as Brunswick."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.643393874168396,
            "question": "What city held the administrative center of the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5552313327789307,
            "question": "Which city would have been the center of political activity during the existence of the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.512886106967926,
            "question": "Where is the historical seat of power for the Duchy of Brunswick located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5067850947380066,
            "question": "Historically, what city served as the seat of government for the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of the Duchy of Brunswick is Braunschweig.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8922_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is the historical seat of power for the Duchy of Brunswick located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8922_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city would have been the center of political activity during the existence of the Duchy of Brunswick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8922_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city held the administrative center of the Duchy of Brunswick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8922_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8922_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents mention the city or town of Braunschweig as being related to the Duchy of Brunswick, with two of them specifically stating that it was its capital. There are no indications in the provided texts that contradict this assertion."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided explicitly state that \"Its capital was the city of Brunswick (Braunschweig)\" in reference to the Duchy of Brunswick, supporting the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}